[{"answer": "I reject the idea that asking a hedge fund manager to pay the same tax rate as a plumber or a teacher is class warfare.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Also, is this any way to start a class war?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, I just don't think there's anything to that.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "How does the White House counter that argument?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Well, I just want to -- I want to remind you that the public overwhelmingly thinks a long-term deficit reduction plan should have a combination of spending restraint with asking the most well-off and largest companies to pay a bit more --", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "What's plan B?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, I would remind that you the speaker of the House did for a period of several weeks negotiate with this president and did express a willingness to have $800 billion in additional revenues as part of a package.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "So I repeat, what are you going to do if, as seems likely, the Republicans say sorry, no?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Let me tell you what my reaction is.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "What is the White House reaction to that?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "You know if you're someone like me meeting with him every day, you don't feel like he's ever lost it.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Do you think he's up and running now for the forthcoming election battle?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "It's exactly what we should be doing across America is to have an active, strategic government that is intervening in the economy, not a big government, but to help create jobs in America.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Why can he not replicate that on to a wider economic stage in America and what should he be doing?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, I agree with that.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "How do you keep those kind of jobs or get advanced manufacturing jobs in America?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "This is a really important question because companies are not going to be loyal to a particular country.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "To take that manufacturing?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Our passivity is their opportunity.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Because they'll be standing in the meantime, right?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Are you encouraged by President Obama's demeanor today?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Taking off the gloves.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "-- and pathetic, and rolling over to these Republicans?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "It's totally great.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Is he now doing this?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "The way you do it, one, is you take it to their district.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Can he challenge the convention of modern Washington politics?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, you know, election is always about a choice.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "I mean how is he going to pull this back for the election next year?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Because it was all about a choice.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "How did you turn things around?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I think that he has a good case -- well, I mean, for example, Governor Perry, I think he'll have a tough time, for example, in, you know, the northeast, in the upper Midwest.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Who would you least like to face?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "And I think he's got an argument against the Republicans.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "What if unemployment figures, despite everything the president's currently trying to do, actually go up between now and next November?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Do you see that?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "You heard what she said.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "If ever a possible scenario?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "ORGAN: It's when Arnold Schwarzenegger was caught with his trousers down with the nanny.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "What are you pulling out?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I'm just saying that the temptations for female governors are probably just not as great as they are for men.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Are you basically implying that only female governors can keep their pants on?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "You never got any good offers?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "We don't have -- I don't have any staffers coming and putting notes in my pocket.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "You know what the deal is, is that women in power are much less attractive to men, I think, than men in power are attractive to women.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "You never get -- in the whole time you were governor, you never got a single inappropriate approach?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Do you think so?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I just -- I don't think that -- I think that male power and sex go together but women power, it's -- it's just not -- it doesn't have the same ring.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Is it because you're more terrifying?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Do you think Obama's going to win?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "No, I really don't", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "ORGAN: Do you have any doubts?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, the book doesn't publish until tomorrow.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Are you taken aback by the reaction to your tome?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "You know, I've never met the woman.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Do you like Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Of course, really -- he cannot -- I mean, Todd seriously can't believe that I have an obsession with his wife.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "You would say that, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "CGINNISS: I never had any kind of a look.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "You never had a sneaky look?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "The house was given to me.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Why did you want to be next to them?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "I looked at the house above the fence, if I'm facing in that direction, but I had no interest in what was going on the other side.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "You were looking at a lake?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "The Palins have intimidated so many people for so long in the Wasilla area that it's very hard to find people willing to talk about them even in inconsequential ways on the record.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Would it have carried more weight?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Last summer, I was threatened over and over and over again.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Were you threatened?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "By people who got my e-mail address from a right wing radio talk show host.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Who by?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Nobody directly.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Anybody connected to the Palins?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Yes, many death threats.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Any death threats?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Against you?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "I think it's pretty wonderful.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "It's a bit weird, isn't it?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "I have no idea except what I read it in \"the National Enquirer\" and --", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Do you think she had the affair?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "No, but I substantiated this.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "But as a prestigious journalist -- let me ask you, as a prestigious journalist, do you just willy-nilly repeat \"National Enquirer\" scoops even if you can't substantiate them?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I substantiated it by talking to many, many people.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "So it is true?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Yes, it is true.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "So it is true?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "That's your terminology.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Is that the same as being a sex cheat?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "She made a mistake.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Is it or not?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Did you say that in the book?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I'm not asking anyone to draw any particular inference.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "You wrote the book?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "I wasn't trying to make anyone draw any inference.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Let me ask you then, in simple language that you feel comfortable, what was the inference you were trying to make us draw from that anecdote?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Do you think she's going to run as president?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "At this point, I'm not sure it matters.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "You still hope she does for book sales, right?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Not fully.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Have you been able to get your head around what happened, to understand why it happened?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Yes, because it was a working day.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Would you normally have been in your office that day?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I don't think so, because I was in the -- my office is in the 16th and the 17th floor.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Would you have been hurt, do you know?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I was phoned by some of the people that escaped the island.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Where did you hear about that and what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Yes, I know several of the people who died.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Did you know any of the people who died?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "The main answer is that we are going to go through everything that happened, the response of the police, the health system, everything.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "How do you answer that?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Again, I think it will be wrong to jump to conclusions.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Was there a failure, do you think, on the intelligence side, to not pick up on somebody like him earlier?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Actually, I don't have so much feelings about him at all.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "What are your feelings toward the man that did this?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "As prime minister of Norway, I fully understand him, because compared to, for instance, Norway, rich people pay much less taxes in the U.S. than in Norway.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "What is your reaction to that as a world leader?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "In Norway, the average tax on people earning more than one million will be around 50 percent or something.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "What is the comparative taxation?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "So significantly higher?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "I'm concerned.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "What's your overview?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "I believe that it's dangerous to say that all those scientists are telling us that this is dangerous were wrong.", "docId": "110919pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "How would you feel if one of them became president?", "qSentId": 660}]